Tufts Student Resources Records UA163
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Student Resources Records
1985 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Student Resources
UA163
0.55 Linear Feet 1 box
1 Web sites
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: The Weekly Peek; and Web crawls.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of slides used for "The Weekly Peek" project, an advertising and promotional device located in the Mayer Campus Center, and web crawls documenting Tufts Students Resources' web presence. The "Weekly Peek" was a projection booth that used random candid pictures of students in everyday activities. The slides also include advertisements directed to the Tufts University market.
Related Materials
UP173; Freshman Directories
Biographical / Historical
TSR is a semi-autonomous, non-profit, student-run business organization founded in 1981 at Tufts University whose primary goals include: Providing the University community with needed services and goods. Offering employment and work-study opportunities to Tufts University students. Providing a medium in which students can gain business management and entrepreneurial experience without the investment of personal capital. Tufts Student Resources has been providing the Tufts community with the goods, services, employment, and business experience all while maintaining its status of being student-run. Advised by a Board of Directors, consisting of representatives from the Dean of Students, Student Activities, Student Employment, and other departments of the University, TSR has established itself as entirely financially independent of the University. In addition, TSR has become one of the most important organizations on campus. TSR currently encompasses seven divisions declaring annual revenues of $180,000 while employing approximately 60 students.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Student life; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations
- The Weekly Peek, 1985 -- 1987; UA163.001; 0.55 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains slides used for The Weekly Peek, a continuous slide presentation of student life at Tufts shown in the Mayer Campus Center. Tufts Student Resources sold ads to be intersperced in this slide show to generate revenue.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Weekly Peek [documentation], 1985; UA163.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Weekly Peek [documentation], 1986 -- 1987; UA163.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Weekly Peek [slides], 1985 -- 1987; UA163.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Weekly Peek [slides], 1985 -- 1987; UA163.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Weekly Peek [slides], 1985 -- 1987; UA163.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Weekly Peek [slides], 1985 -- 1987; UA163.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Weekly Peek [slides], 1985 -- 1987; UA163.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Weekly Peek [slides], 1985 -- 1987; UA163.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2020; UA163.002; 1 Web sites
  Quarterly web crawls of the Tufts Student Resources website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - Tufts Student Resources, 2015 -- 2020; UA163.002.00001
    General
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.